One dream,
one wish If you want it,
gotta go over the top!
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no!
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry!
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you?
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, I
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way?
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day?
Then make sure your only
thought you have is Yes, I can!
As you're on your way?
Marks maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you?
Dream living, that's the way!
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today!
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top!
Well, answer my question.
This will be your only chance to do so.
Who exactly are you?
And what were you up to?
If you speak honestly, then we shall
reward you with a painless death.
Do think it over.
Your other option is agonizing torture.
Of course.
My name is Ushimitsu Koza.
The flow of money through the
capital is of interest to me.
My apologies.
Is that so?
Then I am to assume this
is a research mission
to determine the target
of your next heist.
That's quite a clever answer.
But I know as well as you do.
That's not your real name.
I have you now.
Seeing how you moved, I know
you're not an average geisha.
Ushimitsu Koza may be a famous thief,
but you should at least have the decency
to take responsibility for your own crimes.
Very bold, but he would not strike again
so soon after his last move in the capital.
I'm growing impatient.
I'll ask one more time!
Go on, tell us your business!
Your silence has indicated
that you prefer to be tortured!
Very well
What's your hair?
Huh?
She's gone! What the?
Where did she go?
Too close.
Glad I used a Shadow Clone Jutsu.
This is Aurobi.
Honami. Shinobu. Bonkichi.
My apologies, but my cover was blown.
Find somewhere to hide! Yikes.
That is not good.
I can't believe they
were able to thwart you.
There are some ninjas
on patrol. Be careful.
Probably about 11 or so.
Whoa, there are that many? Huh?
Fukuro Cage.
That's the name of their leader.
They're part of a dangerous
group called the Oniwabanshu,
the best of the best in Wano.
I'm sure they're seeking
Orobi as we speak.
We have to find her. Let's go.
Listen, tell us where you are.
Hey, you looking for something, Kashi?
That's right.
How'd you make it out here?
Oh, goodness, do you need a hand?
Sorry, I had a bit too much to drink.
I need a piss so I can hit
some more of that sake.
She hung up.
We have to find her
ourselves in that case.
Hey, Brooke, did you hear?
Locate Robin and protect her.
Loud and clear.
I'll search for her now. Galick.
I finally got to do something fun,
but I suppose it was too good to last.
A curse upon you!
Is she also a ninja?
Perhaps it was a projection.
It doesn't matter if
it's ninjutsu or sorcery.
Her original body should be nearby.
Find her!
Lord Orochi is still having a banquet.
He must not be troubled with this. Now go!
Exterminate this meddling rat!
Come on, let's go.
Drink up.
Easy.
Slow down.
Everyone enjoying themselves?
Hey, it's Odobe, the new girl!
Where have you been all night?
Come sit with me!
As you wish.
A wise man hides a leaf in the forest.
There's no escaping now.
And I still have work to do.
Forgive me for neglecting you.
Would you like some more sake?
My lord?
Orobi?
I'll search for her until I'm exhausted.
Oh, wait.
Should've said bone-tired.
Who is that what are you doing
over there where'd they go
Are you all looking for
something, gentlemen?
The castle is haunted!
This is a nightmare!
My, and you bring these
treasures to the island?
They sound rather lavish.
It's tradition.
Would you like to hear more?
Please ask me anything.
I insist really I suppose
if it's all right.
I do wish to get more acquainted
with you my lord It sounds to
me like you're interested in
becoming my consort or to be dear
Come on a sucky.
Oh, why must you be so cruel my lord?
Now now don't soap.
There's plenty of me to go around kay.
You are too cute my darling
girl I can't help but wonder,
does Lord Orochi know
what she's really like?
For someone of her beauty,
I would wager the Shogun would
overlook just about anything.
Adorable!
Is there something the
matter, Orochi? It's nothing.
Here, my lord. Enjoy.
When Komala Saki pours, the sake runs
deeper, straight down to my soul.
The Oden truly is
beautiful beyond measure.
Oh, how I wish I were the Shogun.
I will admit her hidden dark side
has me a bit terrified, though.
That woman would never give a
man like you the time of day.
Tell him.
Hey, she was trained in your
pleasure hall, wasn't she, boss?
You must have used a firm
hand to keep her in place.
But that's a story.
It seems you've mistaken a
geisha for a pet dog, my friend.
People are like flowers.
You must become the fresh
water at their roots.
Otherwise, how are they to truly bloom?
You got me there, boss.
What's this about
summoning the Toby Rope to
do your bidding against
one measly Sabo cook,
huh?
Your retribution is fierce.
As Yakuza, we take great
pride in our family.
Once one shares the ritual cup,
they are protected for life.
Tell me,
if your child came home beaten to a pulp,
would you not take action on their behalf?
That chivalrous spirit of yours
never fails to impress, boss.
We see eye to eye, Kyoshiro.
One's enemy must be crushed
with an overwhelming force.
Cripple them so they may
never face you again.
Spare your foes no mercy, even if
they're nothing but an old ghost.
That beating your underlings, Toki,
isn't the only issue here, Kyoshiro.
We have strangers
sneaking into the capital.
This is a big deal.
I've said it once and I'll say it again.
So listen carefully or pay the price.
The time has come.
It's the 20th anniversary
of Kozuki Odin's death.
His wife Toki said their
revenge would come this year.
The Kozuki legacy persists even now!
Ha!
You can't get enough of that ghost story.
But we've long since
buried the Kozuki clan.
Right, Komurasaki?
Let me remind you!
Odin's retainers, the Akazaya Nine,
were frightfully powerful
and loyal as they come!
Their leader, Kin'emon, is
brave and crafty as a fox too!
They've undoubtedly returned to the
land of Wano as part of some scheme.
They'll come for my head soon.
I can see their faces now.
They won't be satisfied till
they take their revenge.
We've wiped out so many Kozuki clan folks.
There's no one left to
be afraid of anymore.
The whole thing seems
kind of pathetic to me.
Someone fought the Yokozuna and Kuri.
Then they had the nerve
to go after Jack's men!
And Kaido himself had to step in.
Then there was that sober cook.
And that Ronin at the gambling
hall defying the Yakuza?
What if they were all attacking
under Kinemon's orders?
Foxfire Kin'emon and the Akazaya Samurai.
If they want to challenge
us, then I welcome it.
I'll send them right back to
their graves with a single stroke.
Hehehehehehe!
Dependable is always good show!
I know Odin is dead.
He fell right before my hides.
But his son, Lomonoski, is
still alive out there somewhere!
Hm?
His body was never recovered!
And that goes to several
of Odin's retainers too!
The Kozuki clan yet lives!
As we speak, they're probably
out there gathering more allies!
What?!
They'll take Kaido's head too
once they're done with me!
It's only a matter of
time before they come!
They're gonna take Kaido's head?!
You gotta be kidding me!
I know the Shogun's a
chicken, but come on!
Keep it down!
If he hears you talking like that,
it's your head that's gonna roll!
Okay, cool.
Take this one next.
Okay!
Hey, I'm Adam Saki! Yes,
sir. Be right there.
Get that to him, if you would. Okay!
Don't make me tell you this again!
We're in the final year now!
Toki's dying words made it quite clear!
That means we'd be
foolish not to heed them!
He's such a coward.
Pathetic, huh?
It's just a poem.
Can't over it.
You are the moon unaware of the dawn.
Here we go again.
This really ruins the sake.
May your purpose be fulfilled and
cast nine shadows on the night
woven of 20 years and you shall
know the brilliance of the dawn.
Need I tell you what that means?
20 years from Toki's death
on a ghostly moonlit night,
nine samurai will appear
to settle their own grudge.
They'll kill me.
Then carry out his will, they'll open up
the land of Wano to the rest of the world!
Interesting that he takes
the prophecy so seriously.
Though it's no surprise that his
subordinates don't share his position.
Convenient for us.
Shogun's lost yet.
Oh, your enemies are long
dead, you delusional fool.
Nobody has cared for years.
Oh, grow up.
It's just an old fairy tale.
They can't win.
Don't give those bastards an inch.
Stay vigilant.
There are deadly enemies lying in wait.
Who is that?
You can't laugh at the Shogun.
He'll have you killed.
Who was that?
You'd better not be laughing at me!
Walter, go stop.
He's so serious!
But everyone thinks the
Shogun is a big bull!
Get that girl out of here!
Sorry you guys!
I can't stop!
Sounds like a child!
It must be Oidon's assistant!
Shut her up!
Hotako, please!
I know! I know!
I shouldn't laugh!
You mock me?
Don't forget I rule this country!
Shut that girl up!
The grudge from 20 years past!
You think me a coward?
You think that I still fear Odin?
You should fear me!
I win that battle long ago!
Shogun!
Odin fell to me!
Please, I thank you!
Leave her be!
Oiron, what can she do?
Watch, she's probably scheming something.
My lord, the poor girl's just a child.
Stay out of this, Komurasaki!
My lord, please forgive her!
Did you laugh at me you little rat?
You'll pay!
She doesn't mean to.
She can't help it.
Don't let him kill her.
It's far too late to stop him!
He'll kill us too.
Give it up!
My lord I beg of you!
Have mercy!
Shut your filthy mouth and listen to!
Don't laugh at me?
How to go.
Komurasaki, why would you
do such a thing to me?
Apologize!
Bow your head!
Get on your knees and grind
your forehead into the floor!
I'll do no such thing!
I won't grovel.
I kneel before no one.
The audacity!
I will not give an inch, you hear me?
Not when I know that I am in the right.
Why?
You've thrown it all away.
I'd made up my mind.
I was going to give you
the greatest honor of all.
You were to be my wife.
If you want some docile
wife with no spine,
then please go ahead and
cut me down I am the daughter
of a samurai that's enough I
I refuse to live in disgrace.
You've got some nerve, woman.
You're nothing but a glorified whore!
And you don't know a
damn thing about Samurai!
What happened to him?
The Shogun transformed.
Gomorrah Saki!
But it's such a pity!
I would hate to see beauty
such as yours go to waste,
crushed to pieces in my powerful jaw!
Thou to me!
Apologize and plead for your life.
Then I'll grant you a lighter sentence.
It's a generous offer.
What are you waiting for?
Apologize from the bottom of your heart.
You should learn to let things go.
They say whoever falls in love loses.
What?
I will not beg.
Not even for my life.
Why is she provoking him?
Stop it!
Komurasaki!
How dare you!
THREE INCOMING!
My lord, why?
What did we do to earn your wrath?
Arrogant wench!
Wait, you're the lady for the Sofa Show.
Why are you here?
Never mind that.
I'm just glad that you weren't hurt.
Where did that sorceress go?
She must be close.
Thought you could fool us, huh?
You're not going anywhere,
you wicked little snoop.
Over here, everyone.
I found our prey.
Someone help!
Have it your way, Komurasaki.
If you won't submit, then I'll
crush you today personally.
He-he-he-he-he!
This is pandemonium!
Any last words?
Very well, then.
Daegoku!
The Shogun's gone wild!
Quick, use some ninja tricks!
Save the Oiran!
The Shogun's the boss here.
The man's free to do whatever he wants.
Besides, we have our own problems.
More specifically, her.
Invaders must be dealt with swiftly.
You mean the geisha?
So is Oro be some kind of spy?
I should have known.
I've never seen her before, but
I didn't think anything of it.
You gotta help, lady!
The Oro's gonna die!
There's nothing I can do.
Saving you will prove difficult enough.
I'm in a fair bit of danger myself.
Someone help me!
He'll curse us to death!
What the hell's going on over there?
U-Gene, Rai-Gene, what are
you two screaming about?
It must be some sort of Yo-Kai.
A giant skeleton, a Gashadokuro.
A curse upon you.
What?
It's a ghost!
She passed out.
A curse upon you!
I'm pleased to see you're safe. That
I am. Thank you. That was close.
Does this color look good on me?
It's amazing and keep it up.
Let's escape this place together.
It can't be.
The sorceress and the ghost are allies.
It's time for Mellow Fleur!
Panhegan Testo Moon!
Jazzy tricks!
We'll stop you!
Huh?
It's over!
It's a yokai!
Shall I escort you to
the land of the dead?
Come along, please.
Go away!
This has turned into a real mess.
What should we do?
Alas, there's not much
point in hiding now.
Perhaps we can help them out.
All right, let's go.
Who attacked us? A ninja?
Do my ears deceive me, or did
that woman just call you Shinobu?
So it's you, Highness!
You're still alive, you bewitching
vixen, you seductress kunoichi!
Shinobu, the man-killer!
Recognized me right away.
No, my mistake.
She was much hotter.
I'll screw you!
NINPO!
Ball crusher technique!
That's not much of a technique.
Oh, no mistaking it.
That's her signature attack.
It's why they call her the Mad Killer.
She does it that much?
I-I can't move.
NINPO!
Coralysis Jutsu! Huh?
You made that up!
Let us depart.
I shall lead the way.
Sexy NINPO!
Rot garden!
Ha!
What's with these ninjas
falling through the ceiling?
That's Highness!
But who are the Konoichi?
The Banquet Hall is a mess!
What the hell is going on here?
Anami. Oh, hello.
Shall I curse you too?
No, thank you.
Anami.
I came here to back you up.
Where did you go, Korosaki?
There you are.
Kyoshiro!
You should not have done that, Komodosaki.
Prepared to die?
I fear nothing.
I don't know.
Oh, my God.
No!
How could he?
She's dead!
Sir Kyoshiro, why did you do such a thing?
The most beautiful woman in all of Wano.
It's a tragedy.
Komurasaki.
What were you thinking, Kyoshiro?
I didn't order you to kill her, damn it!
How dare you!
I granted her a mercy.
That is to say, she had a samurai's death.
No matter who is the offender,
no one rebels against the Shogun.
The rules are absolute.
Is the sub-twisted way
to show his loyalty?
What does he need to prove?
He's gone too far.
Give me that child!
I'm not done here!
I will be satisfied
when I crush your bones!
If you hadn't laughed at me,
Cobra Saki would still be alive!
You rotten little feats!
What the hell are you totting, Otterby?
Pender over!
Otterby!
He's him! Come out!
Oh boy, oh boy!
You really wanted to see me?
I bet you'd love a weather egg, huh?
You bet!
A curse upon you.
We have an intruder to deal with.
There's no time to be running in terror!
A curse upon you.
He's not really attacking us though.
A curse upon you. I say!
I noticed. Uh-oh.
I suppose I can excuse myself now. Oh, no!
Hurry!
Intruders!
To the banquet room!
We must fight!
Capture the wicked sorceress!
Her ninja allies, too!
Go forth and quell Lord Odorchi's rage!
Watch the floor! Ready?
Neen-Po!
Lightning plant!
What the hell?
The power of youth.
Your ninpo is wild but mighty.
That was close!
Splendid work.
You saved us.
This is Oshiroko.
Go ahead and try it, Olen.
Oh, my.
It smells lovely.
I'm so hungry, too.
Goodness!
Heavenly!
It's so sweet, I've never
had anything like it.
Well, thank you.
I'm pleased to hear it.
But forgive me, I'm
afraid that's all we have.
I wish I could eat it all day.
But I know you shared
as much as you could.
That means so much to me.
She seems nice, but you said she's
strong and scary, too? Uh-huh.
As strong as they come.
Then we should ask her
to save Luffy Toto from
the bad guys while she's
still being friendly. What?
Oh, a fine idea.
We'd be playing with fire.
There's got to be a million and one
ways that plan could go sideways.
We still got to try.
Let's do it. Agreed.
You know what we're getting into right
when she gets her memory back we could die
that's better than waiting and doing nothing
we have to try this is our big chance?
What is it, my darling little friend?
Hold hands.
I'm so hungry today.
I could use another snack.
No!
Our friend needs your aid. Help us.
Let's go to Udon together, okay?
I suppose.
I don't know anything about
Udon, though. Don't worry.
Oh, and I heard a rumor.
The guy in charge of Udon
likes Oshiruko as much as you.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's what I heard, too.
I bet they have tons of it there.
Oh, I got swept away in their life.
If she can't get the food
he promised, she'll kill me!
She'll kill us all!
Really?
So I can get my new favorite treat?
Let's get a move on!